A Guide to the Records of the Public Library Development Division of the Virginia State Library and Archives, 1920-1992
Library of Virginia
- Series II. Library Consultant files, 1968-1987., Extent: 13.65 cubic feet (39 boxes). (Box 130-168)
  - Area I files, 1968-1987.
    - Pearisburg Public Library, 1975-1976. (Box 139, Folder 8)
    - Pearisburg Public Library, 1972-1974. (Box 139, Folder 9)
    - Pearisburg Public Library, 1969-1971. (Box 139, Folder 10)
    - Pittsylvania County Public Library, 1971-1979. (Box 139, Folder 11)
    - Pulaski County Library, 1980-1986. (Box 139, Folder 12)
    - Pulaski County Library, 1972-1979. (Box 139, Folder 13)
    - Radford Public Library, 1980-1987. (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - Radford Public Library, 1971-1979. (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - Roanoke County Public Library, 1978-1987. (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - Roanoke County Public Library, 1971-1978. (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - Roanoke (City) Public Library, 1978-1986. (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - Roanoke (City) Public Library, 1974-1977. (Box 140, Folder 6)
    - Roanoke (City) Public Library, 1971-1973. (Box 140, Folder 7)
    - Roanoke Valley Library System, 1971-1974. (Box 140, Folder 8)
    - Russell County Public Library, 1975-1986. (Box 140, Folder 9)
    - Salem Public Library, 1971-1987. (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - Smyth - Bland Regional Library, 1976-1987. (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - Smyth - Bland Regional Library, 1971-1975. (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - Tazewell Public Library, 1983-1986. (Box 141, Folder 4)
    - Tazewell Public Library, 1971-1982. (Box 141, Folder 5)
    - Vaughan Memorial Library, 1971-1982. (Box 141, Folder 6)
    - Washington County Public Library, 1979-1987. (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - Washington County Public Library, 1971-1978. (Box 142, Folder 2)
    - Wythe - Grayson Regional Library, 1981-1987. (Box 142, Folder 3)
    - Wythe - Grayson Regional Library, 1977-1980. (Box 142, Folder 4)
    - Wythe - Grayson Regional Library, 1974-1976. (Box 142, Folder 5)
    - Wythe - Grayson Regional Library, 1971-1973. (Box 142, Folder 6)
  - Area II files, 1968-1987.
    - Governor's Conference on Library and Information Science, 1978-1979. (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - Governor's Conference on Library and Information Science, 1978-1979. (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - Personnel, 1971-1986. (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous, 1979-1987. (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - Piedmont Mailbox Library, 1974-1976. (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - Piedmont Mailbox Library, 1974-1976. (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - Piedmont Mailbox Library, 1974-1976. (Box 143, Folder 7)
    - Piedmont Mailbox Library, 1974-1976. (Box 143, Folder 8)
    - Piedmont Mailbox Library, 1974-1976. (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - Piedmont Mailbox Library, 1974-1975. (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - Piedmonst Mailbox Library, 1975-1976. (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - Piedmont Mailbox Library - Catalogs, 1974-1976. (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Library Association, 1970-1974. (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Library Association - Conference, 1969. (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Library Association - Conference, 1971. (Box 144, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Library Association - Conference, 1972. (Box 144, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Library Association - Conference, 1973. (Box 144, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Library Association - Conference, 1975. (Box 144, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Library Association - Conference, 1976. (Box 144, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Library Association - Conference, 1977. (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Library Association - Conference, 1978. (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Library Association - Conference, 1979. (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Library Association - Conference, 1980. (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - West Piedmont Planning District, 1973-1975. (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Amelia County (James L. Hamner Public Library), 1971-1978. (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Amherst County Public Library, 1970-1983. (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - Augusta County Library, 1977-1985. (Box 145, Folder 8)
    - Augusta County Library, 1972-1976. (Box 145, Folder 9)
    - Bedford County Public Library, 1976-1981. (Box 145, Folder 10)
    - Bedford County Public Library, 1971-1975. (Box 145, Folder 11)
    - Bedford Regional Library, 1980-1985. (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - Botetourt-Rockbridge Regional Library, 1977-1978. (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Botetourt-Rockbridge Regional Library, 1975-1976. (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - Botetourt-Rockbridge Regional Library, 1971-1974. (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - Buckingham County, 1973-1983. (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - Campbell County Public Library, 1975-1983. (Box 146, Folder 6)
    - Campbell County Public Library, 1969-1974. (Box 146, Folder 7)
    - Culpeper Town and County Library, 1975-1983. (Box 146, Folder 8)
    - Culpeper Town and County Library, 1970-1974. (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - Cumberland County Public Library, 1970-1976. (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Farmville Public Library, 1970-1982. (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - Farmville Reading Room, 1971-1981. (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Farmville - Proposed Regional Library, 1971-1977. (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - Farmville - Proposed Regional Library, 1971-1977. (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - Fauquier County Public Library, 1976-1983. (Box 147, Folder 7)
    - Fauquier County Public Library, 1968-1975. (Box 147, Folder 8)
    - Fluvanna County Library, 1971-1983. (Box 147, Folder 9)
    - Halifax County-South Boston Regional Library, 1971-1981. (Box 147, Folder 10)
    - Highland County Public Library, 1982-1985. (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Jefferson-Madison Regional Library, 1983. (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - Jefferson-Madison Regional Library, 1982. (Box 148, Folder 3)
    - Jefferson-Madison Regional Library, 1981. (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - Jefferson-Madison Regional Library, 1980. (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - Jefferson-Madison Regional Library, 1979. (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - Jefferson-Madison Regional Library, 1978. (Box 148, Folder 7)
    - Jefferson-Madison Regional Library, 1977. (Box 148, Folder 8)
    - Jefferson-Madison Regional Library, 1976. (Box 148, Folder 9)
    - Jefferson-Madison Regional Library, 1974-1975. (Box 148, Folder 10)
    - Jefferson-Madison Regional Library, 1973. (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - Jefferson-Madison Regional Library, 1972. (Box 149, Folder 2)
    - Jefferson-Madison Regional Library, 1971. (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - Jefferson-Madison Regional Library, 1965-1970. (Box 149, Folder 4)
    - Jones Memorial Library, 1969-1985. (Box 149, Folder 5)
    - Lynchburg Area, 1982-1983. (Box 149, Folder 6)
    - Lynchburg Area, 1980-1981. (Box 149, Folder 7)
    - Lynchburg Area, 1974-1979. (Box 149, Folder 8)
    - Lynchburg Area, 1973. (Box 149, Folder 9)
    - Lynchburg Area, 1970-1972. (Box 149, Folder 10)
    - Lynchburg Public Library, 1982-1983. (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - Lynchburg Public Library, 1980-1981. (Box 150, Folder 2)
    - Lynchburg Public Library, 1978-1979. (Box 150, Folder 3)
    - Lynchburg Public Library, 1977. (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - Lynchburg Public Library, 1975-1976. (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - Lynchburg Public Library, 1971-1974. (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - Madison County Library, 1975-1983. (Box 150, Folder 7)
    - Madison County Library, 1971-1974. (Box 150, Folder 8)
    - Nottoway County Library, 1971-1983. (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - Orange County Public Library, 1975-1983. (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - Orange County Public Library, 1971-1974. (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Prince Edward County, 1976-1983. (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - Rappahannock County Library, 1975-1983. (Box 151, Folder 5)
    - Rappahannock County Library, 1971-1974. (Box 151, Folder 6)
    - Rockbridge Regional Library, 1984. (Box 151, Folder 7)
    - Rockbridge Regional Library, 1983. (Box 151, Folder 8)
    - Rockbridge Regional Library, 1983. (Box 151, Folder 9)
    - Rockbridge Regional Library, 1983. (Box 151, Folder 10)
    - Rockbridge Regional Library, 1982. (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - Rockbridge Regional Library, 1982. (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - Rockbridge Regional Library, 1981. (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - Rockbridge Regional Library, 1981. (Box 152, Folder 4)
    - Rockbridge Regional Library, 1980. (Box 152, Folder 5)
    - Rockbridge Regional Library, 1980. (Box 152, Folder 6)
    - Rockbridge Regional Library, 1979. (Box 152, Folder 7)
    - Rockbridge Regional Library - Bath County Library Building, 1978-1980. (Box 152, Folder 8)
    - Rockingham Public Library, 1979-1983. (Box 153, Folder 1)
    - Rockingham Public Library, 1971-1978. (Box 153, Folder 2)
    - Shenandoah County, 1978-1984. (Box 153, Folder 3)
    - Shenandoah County, 1974-1977. (Box 153, Folder 4)
    - Shenandoah County, 1970-1973. (Box 153, Folder 5)
    - Shenandoah County - Travel brochures, undated. (Box 153, Folder 6)
    - Southside Regional Library, 1979-1984. (Box 153, Folder 7)
    - Southside Regional Library, 1971-1978. (Box 153, Folder 8)
    - Southside Regional Library - Economic studies, 1973-1974. (Box 153, Folder 9)
    - Staunton Public Library, 1977-1983. (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - Staunton Public Library, 1971-1976. (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - Warren County, 1977-1983. (Box 154, Folder 3)
    - Warren County, 1971-1976. (Box 154, Folder 4)
    - Waynesboro Public Library, 1974-1984. (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - Waynesboro Public Library, 1971-1973. (Box 154, Folder 6)
    - Waynesboro Public Library - Annual reports, 1966-1976. (Box 154, Folder 7)
    - Winchester / Handley Library, 1979-1983. (Box 154, Folder 8)
    - Winchester / Handley Library, 1975-1978. (Box 154, Folder 9)
    - Winchester / Handley Library, 1964-1974. (Box 154, Folder 10)
  - Area III files, 1968-1987.
    - Appomattox Regional Library, 1980-1983. (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - Appomattox Regional Library, 1976-1979. (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - Appomattox Regional Library, 1972-1975. (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - Brunswick - Greensville Regional Library, 1978-1983. (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - Brunswick - Greensville Regional Library, 1974-1977. (Box 155, Folder 5)
    - Brunswick - Greensville Regional Library, 1971-1973. (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - Brunswick - Greensville Regional Library - Clippings, 1980-1981. (Box 155, Folder 7)
    - Brunswick - Greensville Regional Library - Clippings, 1976-1979. (Box 155, Folder 8)
    - Brunswick - Greensville Regional Library - Clippings, 1972-1975. (Box 155, Folder 9)
    - Caroline Library, 1979-1983. (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - Central Rappahannock Regional Library, 1980-1983. (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - Central Rappahannock Regional Library, 1978-1979. (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - Central Rappahannock Regional Library, 1976-1977. (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - Central Rappahannock Regional Library, 1974-1975. (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - Central Rappahannock Regional Library, 1971-1973. (Box 156, Folder 6)
    - Chapman Memorial Library (Smithfield), 1973-1974. (Box 156, Folder 7)
    - Charles H. Taylor Memorial Library (Hampton), 1973-1983. (Box 156, Folder 8)
    - Chesapeake Public Library, 1979-1983. (Box 156, Folder 9)
    - Chesapeake Public Library, 1973-1978. (Box 156, Folder 10)
    - Chesterfield County Public Library, 1978-1983. (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - Chesterfield County Public Library, 1976-1977. (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - Chesterfield County Public Library, 1973-1975. (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - Colonial Heights Public Library, 1979-1983. (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - Colonial Heights Public Library, 1973-1978. (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - Eastern Shore Public Library, 1980-1983. (Box 157, Folder 6)
    - Eastern Shore Public Library, 1975-1979. (Box 157, Folder 7)
    - Essex Public Library, 1974-1983. (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - Franklin Library Association, 1973-1983. (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - Gloucester Library, 1973-1983. (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - Henrico County Public Library, 1981-1985. (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - Henrico County Public Library, 1981-1983. (Box 158, Folder 5)
    - Henrico County Public Library, 1977-1980. (Box 158, Folder 6)
    - Henrico County Public Library, 1973-1976. (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - Heritage Library (Charles City and New Kent), 1983. (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - King and Queen County, 1983. (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - Lancaster County Public Library, 1972-1983. (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - Mathews Memorial Library, 1978-1983. (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - Mathews Memorial Library, 1973-1977. (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - Morgan Memorial Library (Suffolk), 1978-1983. (Box 159, Folder 7)
    - Morgan Memorial Library (Suffolk), 1973-1977. (Box 159, Folder 8)
    - Newport News Public Library, 1977-1983. (Box 159, Folder 9)
    - Newport News Public Library, 1973-1976. (Box 159, Folder 10)
    - Newport News Public Library, 1967-1971. (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Northumberland Memorial Library, 1973-1983. (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Norfolk Public Library, 1980-1983. (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - Norfolk Public Library, 1978-1979. (Box 160, Folder 4)
    - Norfolk Public Library, 1973-1977. (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - Pamunkey Regional Library, 1978-1983. (Box 160, Folder 6)
    - Pamunkey Regional Library, 1977. (Box 160, Folder 7)
    - Pamunkey Regional Library, 1976. (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - Pamunkey Regional Library, 1975-1976. (Box 161, Folder 2)
    - Pamunkey Regional Library, 1973-1975. (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - Petersburg Public Library, 1979-1983. (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - Petersburg Public Library, 1976-1978. (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - Petersburg Public Library, 1973-1975. (Box 161, Folder 6)
    - Poquoson Public Library, 1976-1983. (Box 161, Folder 7)
    - Portsmouth Public Library, 1983. (Box 161, Folder 8)
    - Portsmouth Public Library, 1982. (Box 162, Folder 1)
    - Portsmouth Public Library, 1978-1981. (Box 162, Folder 2)
    - Portsmouth Public Library, 1975-1977. (Box 162, Folder 3)
    - Portsmouth Public Library, 1975. (Box 162, Folder 4)
    - Portsmouth Public Library, 1973-1974. (Box 162, Folder 5)
    - Powhatan County Public Library, 1973-1983. (Box 162, Folder 6)
    - Prince William Public Library, 1979-1983. (Box 162, Folder 7)
    - Prince William Public Library, 1977-1978. (Box 162, Folder 8)
    - Prince William Public Library, 1971-1976. (Box 162, Folder 9)
    - Richmond Public Library, 1978-1983. (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - Richmond Public Library, 1972-1977. (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - Smoot Memorial Library (King George County), 1973-1983. (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - Urbanna Public Library, 1973-1983. (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Beach Public Library, 1978-1983. (Box 163, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Beach Public Library, 1976-1977. (Box 163, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Beach Public Library, 1974-1975. (Box 164, Folder 1)
    - Walter C. Rawls Library, 1980-1983. (Box 164, Folder 2)
    - Walter C. Rawls Library, 1976-1979. (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - Walter C. Rawls Library, 1975. (Box 164, Folder 4)
    - Walter C. Rawls Library, 1968-1975. (Box 164, Folder 5)
    - Williamsburg Regional Public Library, 1978-1983. (Box 164, Folder 6)
    - Williamsburg Regional Public Library, 1973-1978. (Box 165, Folder 1)
    - York County Public Library, 1983. (Box 165, Folder 2)
    - York County Public Library, 1981-1983. (Box 165, Folder 3)
    - , 19. (Box 165)
  - Area IV files, 1968-1987.
    - Alexandria Library, 1978-1983. (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - Alexandria Library, 1971-1978. (Box 166, Folder 2)
    - Arlington County Public Library, 1978-1983. (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - Arlington County Public Library, 1970-1977. (Box 166, Folder 4)
    - Arlington County Library, 1970-1981. (Box 166, Folder 5)
    - Fairfax County Public Library, 1982-1983. (Box 166, Folder 6)
    - Fairfax County Public Library, 1981. (Box 166, Folder 7)
    - Fairfax County Public Library, 1980. (Box 167, Folder 1)
    - Fairfax County Public Library, 1979. (Box 167, Folder 2)
    - Fairfax County Public Library, 1976-1978. (Box 167, Folder 3)
    - Fairfax County Public Library, 1972-1975. (Box 167, Folder 4)
    - Fairfax County Public Library, 1970-1971. (Box 167, Folder 5)
    - Falls Church Public Library, 1979-1983. (Box 167, Folder 6)
    - Falls Church Public Library, 1971-1978. (Box 167, Folder 7)
    - Loudoun County Public Library, 1983. (Box 168, Folder 1)
    - Loudoun County Public Library, 1979-1982. (Box 168, Folder 2)
    - Loudoun County Public Library, 1973-1978. (Box 168, Folder 3)
    - Loudoun County Public Library, 1968-1972. (Box 168, Folder 4)
    - Loudoun County Public Library - Correspondence, 1975-1983. (Box 168, Folder 5)
    - Loudoun County Public Library - Correspondence, 1970-1974. (Box 168, Folder 6)
- Series III. Scrapbooks, 1910-1971., Extent: 1.75 cubic feet (5 boxes). (Box 169-173)
  This series is housed in 5 boxes and includes both original scrapbooks and photocopies of original newsclippings. The bulk of the scrapbooks consist of newspaper articles, but may also include a small amount of correspondence, photographs, programs and other ephemera. Includes the following scrapbooks: County Libraries, 1927-1957; City Libraries, 1910-1956; Regional Public Libraries, 1923-1956; Regional City-County Libraries, 1941-1955; Counties Without Libraries, 1925-1956; Extension Division, 1910-1956; Virginia State Library, 1945-1956; Virginia - General, 1921-1956; Virginia Adult Education Association, 1953-1956; American Library Association, 1954-1955; Virginia Colleges, 1910-1954; Virginia Public Schools, 1939-1954; Virginia Special Libraries, 1931-1955; Virginia Library Association, 1910, 1933-1955; Virginia War Work, 1942-1943; Demonstration Libraries - Amherst County and Lee County, 1971; Demonstration Libraries, Dickenson County and Tazewell County, 1961-1964; Demonstration Libraries - Eastern Shore, 1956-1958; Demonstration Libraries - Prince William County, 1952-1955; Demonstration Libraries - Washington County, 1954-1956; Demonstration Libraries - Wise County, 1958-1960; Works Progress Administration (WPA), 1938-1942.
  - Scrapbooks - County Public Libraries (Photocopied), 1927-1957.
    Originally three County Public Libraries Scrapbooks - A-M, N-P, and R-S.
    - Alleghany County, 1930-1954. (Box 169, Folder 1)
    - Arlington County, 1937-1956. (Box 169, Folder 2)
    - Bedford County, 1946-1955. (Box 169, Folder 3)
    - Charlotte County, 1937-1941. (Box 169, Folder 4)
    - Chesterfield County, 1952-1953. (Box 169, Folder 5)
    - Fairfax County, 1937-1953. (Box 169, Folder 6)
    - Franklin County, 1941-1944. (Box 169, Folder 7)
    - Halifax County, 1938-1955. (Box 169, Folder 8)
    - Lancaster County, 1953-1955. (Box 169, Folder 9)
    - Loudoun County, 1936-1957. (Box 169, Folder 10)
    - Mathews County, 1927-1956. (Box 169, Folder 11)
    - Nottoway County, 1931-1941. (Box 169, Folder 12)
    - Orange County, 1941-1954. (Box 169, Folder 13)
    - Patrick County, 1941; 1951. (Box 169, Folder 14)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1939-1945. (Box 169, Folder 15)
    - Pulaski County, 1946-1956. (Box 169, Folder 16)
    - Roanoke County, 1932-1953. (Box 169, Folder 17)
    - Salem County, 1937-1942. (Box 169, Folder 18)
    - Smyth County, 1947. (Box 169, Folder 19)
  - Scrapbooks - City Libraries (Photocopied), 1910-1956.
    Originally four City Libraries Scrapbooks - A-H, L-P, R and S-W.
    - Alexandria, 1936-1937, 1951. (Box 170, Folder 1)
    - Bristol, 1951. (Box 170, Folder 2)
    - Covington, 1954. (Box 170, Folder 3)
    - Buena Vista-Clifton Forge (empty), undated. (Box 170, Folder 4)
    - Danville, 1923-1956. (Box 170, Folder 5)
    - Falls Church, 1950-1953. (Box 170, Folder 6)
    - Fredericksburg, 1924-1948. (Box 170, Folder 7)
    - Hampton, 1922-1955. (Box 170, Folder 8)
    - Hopewell, 1930-1955. (Box 170, Folder 9)
    - Lynchburg, 1937-1955. (Box 170, Folder 10)
    - Martinsville, 1941-1953. (Box 170, Folder 11)
    - Newport News, 1927-1951. (Box 170, Folder 12)
    - Norfolk, 1912-1952. (Box 170, Folder 13)
    - Petersburg, 1924-1951. (Box 170, Folder 14)
    - Portsmouth, 1910-1951. (Box 170, Folder 15)
    - Richmond, 1911-1913. (Box 170, Folder 16)
    - Richmond, 1945-1950. (Box 170, Folder 17)
    - Richmond, 1951-1956. (Box 170, Folder 18)
    - Roanoke, 1921-1956. (Box 170, Folder 19)
    - South Norfolk, 1950. (Box 170, Folder 20)
    - Staunton, 1927-1952. (Box 170, Folder 21)
    - Staunton, 1953-1955. (Box 170, Folder 22)
    - Suffolk, 1945-1951. (Box 170, Folder 23)
    - Warwick, 1948-1956. (Box 170, Folder 24)
    - Waynesboro, 1943; 1955. (Box 170, Folder 25)
    - Williamsburg, 1941-1956. (Box 170, Folder 26)
    - Winchester, 1925-1953. (Box 170, Folder 27)
  - Scrapbooks - Regional Public Libraries (Photocopied), 1923-1956.
    Originally two Regional Public Libraries Scrapbooks - B-H and R-W.
    - Botetourt-Rockbrige Regional Library, 1946-1955. (Box 171, Folder 1)
    - Brunswick-Greensville Regional Library, 1924-1954. (Box 171, Folder 2)
    - Hanover, Caroline and King William Counties - Pamunkey Regional Library, 1923-1956. (Box 171, Folder 3)
    - Rockingham-Page Regional Library, 1924-1954. (Box 171, Folder 4)
    - Southside Regional Library, 1929-1954. (Box 171, Folder 5)
    - Wythe-Grayson Regional Library, 1937-1954. (Box 171, Folder 6)
  - Scrapbooks - Regional City-County Public Libraries (Photocopied), 1941-1955.
    Originally one scrapbook.
    - Albemarle County and Charlottesville, 1947-1953. (Box 171, Folder 7)
    - Montgomery County and Radford, 1941-1955. (Box 171, Folder 8)
  - Scrapbooks - Counties Without Libraries (Photocopied), 1925-1956.
    - Accomack County, 1946; 1956. (Box 171, Folder 9)
    - Amherst County, 1955. (Box 171, Folder 10)
    - Appomattox County, 1939-1941. (Box 171, Folder 11)
    - Augusta County, 1947. (Box 171, Folder 12)
    - Campbell County, 1940-1952. (Box 171, Folder 13)
    - Craig County, 1947-1951. (Box 171, Folder 14)
    - Dinwiddie County, 1941. (Box 171, Folder 15)
    - Essex County, 1941-1953. (Box 171, Folder 16)
    - Fauquier County, 1926-1928. (Box 171, Folder 17)
    - Gloucester County, 1935-1954. (Box 171, Folder 18)
    - Greene County, 1945-1946. (Box 171, Folder 19)
    - Henrico County, 1925-1956. (Box 171, Folder 20)
    - King and Queen County, 1941. (Box 171, Folder 21)
    - Lancaster County, 1940-1956. (Box 171, Folder 22)
    - Louisa County, 1953-1954. (Box 171, Folder 23)
    - Middlesex County, 1949. (Box 171, Folder 24)
    - Northampton County, 1925-1953. (Box 171, Folder 25)
    - Northumberland County, 1948. (Box 171, Folder 26)
    - Powhatan County, 1939. (Box 172, Folder 1)
    - Prince Edward County, 1941-1953. (Box 172, Folder 2)
    - Southampton County, 1946-1956. (Box 172, Folder 3)
    - Sussex County, 1942-1950. (Box 172, Folder 4)
    - Warren County, 1952-1953. (Box 172, Folder 5)
    - Washington County, 1943. (Box 172, Folder 6)
    - Westmoreland County, 1948-1950. (Box 172, Folder 7)
    - Wise County, 1946-1950. (Box 172, Folder 8)
    - York County, 1931-1952. (Box 172, Folder 9)
  - Scrapbooks - Extension Division (Photocopied), 1910-1956.
    - Extension Division, 1910-1911; 1945-1950. (Box 172, Folder 10)
    - Extension Division, 1951-1956. (Box 172, Folder 11)
  - Scrapbooks - Virginia State Library (Photocopied), 1945-1956.
    - Virginia State Library, 1945-1950. (Box 172, Folder 12)
    - Virginia State Library, 1951-1956. (Box 172, Folder 13)
  - Scrapbooks: Virginia - General (Photocopied), 1921-1956.
    - Virginia - General, 1921-1956. (Box 172, Folder 14)
  - Scrapbooks: Virginia Adult Education Association (Photocopied), 1953-1956.
    - Virginia Adult Education Association, 1953-1956. (Box 172, Folder 14)
  - Scrapbook: Virginia - American Library Association (Photocopied), 1954-1955.
    - American Library Association, 1954-1955. (Box 172, Folder 15)
  - Scrapbook: Virginia Colleges (Photocopied), 1910-1954.
    - Virginia Colleges, 1910-1954. (Box 172, Folder 16)
  - Scrapbook: Virginia Public Schools (Photocopied), 1939-1954.
    - Virginia Public Schools, 1939-1954. (Box 172, Folder 17)